YICHI ZHANG

+1(734) 800-6032 \$\phi\$ yichiz@umich.edu \$\phi\$ Website: https://yichiz97.github.io/4352 North Quad, 510 State St., Ann Arbor, MI 48109, U.S.A.

SUMMARY

I'm a Ph.D. candidate with research focuses on the intersection between computer science and economics, in particular, information elicitation and aggregation, mechanism design, and their interactions with machine learning. Comfortable in using programming and mathematical tools to solve multiagent problems including crowdsourcing, peer grading, peer reviewing, and recommender systems.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Umich)

Sep 2019 - Present

- Ph.D. in School of Information
- Advisor: Grant Schoenebeck

Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU)

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

- B.S. in Electronic Science and Engineering
- Advisor: Xinbing Wang and Luoyi Fu

WORKING EXPERIENCES

University of Michigan, School of Information

Sep 2019 - Present

Research Assistant, Useful Theory Innovation Lab

UCLA, Department of Computer Science

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

Research Intern (The CSST program), working with Mario Gerla

YITUTech Algorithm Engineer Intern

Feb 2019 - May 2019

PUBLICATIONS

Eliciting Informative Text Evaluations with Large Language Models

Yuxuan Lu, Shengwei Xu, **Yichi Zhang**, Yuqing Kong and Grant Schoenebeck In Proceedings of the 25th ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (EC 2024) [https://arxiv.org/abs/2405.15077]

Spot Check Equivalence: an Interpretable Metric for Information Elicitation Mechanisms

Shengwei Xu, **Yichi Zhang**, Paul Resnick and Grant Schoenebeck In Proceedings of the 33nd Annual World Wide Web Conference

(WWW 2024)

[https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.13567]

(Oral presentation)

Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review

Yichi Zhang, Grant Schoenebeck and Weijie Su

In Proceedings of the 38th Annual AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2024)
[https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.14619]

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023) [https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583292]

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023) [https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583334]

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

Yichi Zhang, Fang-Yi Yu, Grant Schoenebeck and David Kempe
In Proceedings of the 23rd ACM Conference on Economics and Computation
[https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09020]
(EC 2022)

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

Grant Schoenebeck, Fang-Yi Yu and **Yichi Zhang** (alphabetically ranked)

In Proceedings of the 30th Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2021)

[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3449840]

POSTERS

Eliciting Effort And Truth-telling From Parties of (No) Interest

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)
- U-M Asian American Faculty & Student Accomplishments Symposium (2022)

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

- DIMACS Workshop on Forecasting (2021)
- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2021)

SELECTED TALKS

Improving Conference Review Via Mechanism Design

• Renmin University of China, Gaoling School of Artificial Intelligence

August 2023

• Peking University, CFCS seminar	July 2023
• University of Michigan, DSCSS seminar	April 2023
• University of Pennsylvania, Wharton Statistics and Data Science	March 2023
• Drexel University, Computer Science Department	March 2023
Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review	
• Harvard University, EconCS seminar	January 2024
TEACHING	
Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich Courses: Big Data Analysis (SI 699) Instructor: Misha Teplitskiy	Winter 2022
Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich	Fall 2021

Course: Deep Learning (SIADS 642) Instructor: Paramveer Dhillon

Course: Network Analysis (SIADS 642)

Instructor: Daniel Romero

AWARDS

• ICSSI Travel Award.	2024
• Rackham Conference Travel Grant, University of Michigan.	2023, 2024
• The Web Conference Student Scholarship.	2021
• Nominee for the Rackham International Student Fellowship, UMSI.	2021
• Outstanding Graduate of Shanghai Jiao Tong University.	2019
• EIC Education Scholarship (top 5%).	2018
• Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).	2017

SERVICE

Reviewer/PC member:

- The Annual Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS): 2024
- The Web Conference (WWW): 2024, 2023, 2022
- The ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (EC): 2023, 2022
- Conference on Web and Internet Economics (WINE): 2023
- International Conference on Computational Social Science (IC2S2): 2024

Organizer:

• The 1st Annual Workshop on Incentives in Academia, jointly organized with EC 2024.